Performance Arts Community Group – Technical Committee meeting
Minutes

Date: September 8m 2020         
Time: 11am ET / 5pm CEST
Attendees:  Julia Beck,  J.Beck@ub.uni-frankfurt.de
                    Klaus Illmayer,  klaus.illmayer@oeaw.ac.at
                    Daniela Rosu, drosu@cs.toronto.edu
                    Gregory Saumier-Finch, gregory@culturecreates.com
                    Birk Weiberg, birk.weiberg@sapa.swiss


Topics discussed:

Admin (15 min)
• communication method: email 
              -> it was agreed to use a “simple” email communication protocol (for now). Decision to     
                   be revisited if the committee’s needs change.

• storage
            -> it was agreed to create a public github repo

• documentation Live OWL Documentation Environment tool (LODE), Widoco
            -> it was agreed to start a shared doc for committee members to indicate their      
                 suggestions/preferences

• auditing – log of changes 
             -> to be decided at the next meeting

Logistics+ (15 min)
• discuss the interaction with the sub-groups of domain experts
           -> the exact nature/composition of the subgroups (if any) to be determined at the 
               first PAIR CG meeting. The interaction between the Technical committee and 
               the groups (if any) will be discussed then as well.

• discuss methodologies for developing and formalizing the technical standard
o discuss modularization, e.g., each module to correspond roughly to the work of a sub-groups?  other?
           -> it was agreed to compile a comparison between existing methodologies and 
               share it via github

Technical Committee Deliverables (15)
• discuss technical deliverables, i.e., (technical) community group reports to be used subsequently as input to a W3C Working Group: use case and requirements, presentation of the representational standard, i.e., notation and namespaces, axiomatization (concepts, properties, rules), dependencies, 
• alignment with existing efforts (semantic and syntactic mappings) 
• usage and best practices guide
      -> it was agreed to revisit this topic during the first meeting of the PAIR-CG group and also   
          to start documenting use cases sourced from the members of the technical committee.

Action items (5 min)
 -> create a github repo for PAIR-CG  (Daniela)
 -> create a use cases report (all members)
 -> compile a comparison matrix between ontology engineering approaches (Daniela)

Other (5min)

Next steps (5 min)  
 -> the next meeting of the Technical Committee to be convened after the first PAIR-CG meeting 

