Performance Arts Community Group – Technical Committee meeting
Agenda

Date: September 8m 2020         
Time: 11am ET / 5pm CEST

Admin (15 min)
• communication method: email 
simple email

• storage github (provided by W3C?) 
• documentation Live OWL Documentation Environment tool (LODE), Widoco
• auditing – log of changes

Logistics+ (15 min)
• discuss the interaction with the sub-groups of domain experts

• discuss methodologies for developing and formalizing the technical standard
o discuss modularization, e.g., each module to correspond roughly to the work of a sub-groups?  other?

Technical Committee Deliverables (15)
• discuss technical deliverables, i.e., (technical) community group reports to be used subsequently as input to a W3C Working Group: use case and requirements, presentation of the representational standard, i.e., notation and namespaces, axiomatization (concepts, properties, rules), dependencies, 
• alignment with existing efforts (semantic and syntactic mappings) 
• usage and best practices guide

Action items (5 min)
• create a github repo  
• start a use cases report 
• compile a comparison matrix between ontology engineering approaches

Other (5min)
Next steps (5 min)  
the next meeting of the Technical Committee to be convened after the first PAIR-CG meeting (in October 2020). 

